{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Who is the youngest sibling of the Bob's Burger family",
      "answers": [
        "Gene",
        "Tina",
        "Louise",
        "Dina"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What is the hair color of Marge Simpson",
      "answers": [
        "Blue",
        "Cyan",
        "Turquoise",
        "Pink"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which one of these is not a song from Titians Go",
      "answers": [
        "Hard!",
        "Catchin Villains",
        "Binary Code",
        "Bad Stuff Happens in the bathroom"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What is the name of Honey's Owner",
      "answers": [
        "Tabitha",
        "Jill",
        "Big Cookie",
        "Lindsay"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which one of these are one of Rogers Personas",
      "answers": [
        "Jeannie Sliver",
        "Martin Plum",
        "Dr.Penquin",
        "Ricky Spam"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which one of these is not a Burger of the Day",
      "answers": [
        "She's A Super Leek Burger",
        "Tunami",
        "Hit Me With Your Best Shallot Burger",
        "Sunny Side Up in Spring Burger"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Who is the principal at steve's school",
      "answers": [
        "Brain Lewis",
        "Barry Robinaon",
        "Toshi Yoshia",
        "Avery Bullock"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What is the species of Linsday on HouseBroken",
      "answers": [
        "Dog",
        "Cat",
        "Shoe",
        "Hamster"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What is Lisa Simspons IQ",
      "answers": [
        "159",
        "130",
        "80",
        "170"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Who is Hailey Smith Husband",
      "answers": [
        "Kalus",
        "Reginald",
        "Avery",
        "Jeff"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3"
    } 
  ]
}